<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WowApp</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">MapsActivity</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_business_profile">BusinessProfile</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="terms_agreement">1- WOW (referred to as "the Company") will notify you in the event that you are selected
to be one of the drivers for this campaign after your selection for the advertising
campaign during the submission period for the campaign.\n
2- Once you are selected, within a period not exceeding (24) hours, you are required to
schedule an appointment with one of the sticker providers through the (WOW)
application. You must attend the appointment at the specified time to avoid any late
penalties that may be incurred.\n
3- The driver must attend at the sticker provider location to have the sticker installed
completely within the specified time. Any fines resulting from delays will be imposed
on the driver and can only be waived by WOW.\n
4- After attending and being present at the scheduled time, please follow the instructions
of the sticker provider to enable them to install the sticker within the specified time and
avoid any delays to prevent overlap with the subsequent appointment.\n
5- After the installation of the advertising campaign sticker on your car, please verify with
the sticker provider that the car has been photographed after the sticker installation
and upload the photos through the (WOW) application.\n
6- You must start the route (Start driving) through the (WOW) application within a period
not exceeding (24) hours from the specified start date of the advertising campaign in
the application. (Any distance traveled or activation of the route before the campaign
start date will not be considered or counted for you. This is to track the route through
the application and start counting the distance traveled)\n
7- After the end of the relevant advertising campaign period, you need to schedule
another appointment with the sticker providers to have the sticker for the related
advertising campaign removed within a period not exceeding (10) ten days from the
end date of the advertising campaign.\n
8- Under no circumstances is it permissible, without the consent of the Company, to
combine two advertising campaigns and install another sticker for the same driver
during the duration of the first campaign and before its full expiration.</string>
</resources>